ed4.net 2012-11-18

# Privacy Policy - e-Dialog.com - e-Dialog - Integrated E-Mail & Cross-Channel Marketing Solutions

Respecting the privacy of our clients and their customers is one of the highest priorities at e-Dialog. We consistently emphasize the importance of our web site visitors’ security and privacy among our employees. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. 

e-Dialog is a member of several associations focused around building and maintaining the integrity of legitimate direct marketers and their email marketing initiatives. These organizations include: 

  * Direct Marketing Association (DMA)
  * Email Sender & Provider Providers Coalition (ESPC)
  * Email Experience Council
  * International Association of Privacy Professionals (IAPP)
  * Messaging Anti-Abuse Working Group (MAAWG)
  * TRUSTe

**Compliance**  
e-Dialog is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program and has been certified compliant to the European Union and Swiss Safe Harbor policies. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.e-dialog.com. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trust mark, this website has agreed to notify you of: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through the web site
  * The organization collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under e-Dialog’s control   

  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact e-Dialog by e-mail at [privacypolicy@e-dialog.com](mailto:privacypolicy@e-dialog.com). 

If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

**Safe Harbor**  
e-Dialog complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland.  e-Dialog has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view e-Dialog’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy or is not in compliance with the Safe Harbor principles, you should first contact e-Dialog’s privacy manager by email at [privacypolicy@e-dialog.com](mailto:privacypolicy@e-dialog.com)

If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact the DMA or TRUSTe Safe Harbor Dispute Resolution Programs. They will then serve as a liaison to e-Dialog to resolve your concerns.

The Direct Marketing Association  
Attn: Ethics/Consumer Affairs Department  
1111 19th Street NW  
Suite 1100  
Washington, DC 20036  
Safeharbor

**Information Collection & Use **  
e-Dialog is the sole owner of the information collected at our site. We do not sell, share or rent information to third parties or partners. The information collected at our site is used exclusively to determine the most appropriate information to send to those who request it.  
Information collected at this site includes: 

  * _Request Information Form:_ Requires users to give us contact information including E-mail address, phone number and company information.
  * _Resume Submissions:_ This information is used only to screen candidates and contact them for interviews.
  * _Log Files:_ We use IP addresses to monitor our site and collect aggregate data for future use. IP addresses are anonymous and are not linked to any individual’s personal information.
  * _Surveys:_ Periodically, e-Dialog will survey our clients for purposes of improving the quality of our service and customer satisfaction. Client participation is completely voluntary.
  * _Sharing:_ Occasionally, e-Dialog may share aggregated information with our clients or partners. This information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. Nor does it disclose confidential or proprietary client information.
  * _Cookies:_ Our website uses Cookies. We use cookies to determine visitor trends and behavior on our website. We do this to improve the service that we offer our clients and visitors. We do not disclose information obtained by the use of cookies to third parties. Our cookies are in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. Client-side cookies may be used to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website. Client-side cookies are also used to track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign. Client-side cookies are in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of our Website.
  * _P3P Policy:_ The Platform for Privacy Preferences Project (P3P), developed by the World Wide Web Consortium, is emerging as an industry standard providing a simple, automated way for users to gain more control over the use of personal information on Web sites they visit. To view our P3P policy, visit http://www.e-dialog.com/w3c/policy.xml. Ad Server Relationships: We do not partner with or have special relationships with ad server companies.

**Security & Privacy**  
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our clients and their customers is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of information, utilizing encryption software. We store the information in a database in a secure environment at a Class A Internet service provider.

Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access, each having signed comprehensive nondisclosure agreements, which provide explicit legal confidentiality protections. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Update & Choice **  
All e-mail sent by e-Dialog will contain clear and concise instructions (such as clicking on the link at the bottom of an e-mail) for how to opt-out of receiving future communications.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information that we maintain about them. Visitors have the ability to correct or remove their contact information or update their profiles by sending an e-mail [to profile update](mailto:updateprofile@e-dialog.com). All requests will be honored within 10 days of the user notification.

**Links**   
The e-Dialog website may contain links to other sites. e-Dialog is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their policies may differ from ours.

**Notification of Changes**  
This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the website. Please check this site for information about revisions to our privacy policy.   
If there is a material change to our privacy policy, we will post notification on our homepage.  
If there is a material change to personally identifiable information, we will notify you by e-mail and provide the ability to opt out of these new uses.

**Client E-Mail Campaigns**  
In some cases, e-Dialog stores database lists from our clients. These lists may contain e-mail addresses, street address, contact information and other relevant information. Confidentiality of the client list is a top priority. e-Dialog is contractually bound to keep our clients’ customer data private. A client’s list is never shared with other clients, partners, etc., and is treated as an asset of our client.

e-Dialog tracks if a recipient has the ability to support HTML e-mail in their e-mail client, as well as whether an HTML e-mail message has been opened or previewed. This capability is used only to deliver the best content to the recipient, and the recipient always has control to change their profile by contacting the client for whom the campaign was deployed.

Information regarding the activity of e-mail recipients is only reported to the client who deployed the e-mail through e-Dialog. Information about specific e-mail recipients is only shared with the client who owns the list on which the e-mail recipients e-mail address originally appeared.

Some e-Dialog clients use Campaign Builder, a self-service product to send their own e-mail campaigns. e-Dialog’s policy against sending unsolicited commercial e-mail applies to this product as well. If e-Dialog determines that a client has knowingly used our system for sending unsolicited commercial e-mail, e-Dialog will revoke the right of this client to send e-mail using our product and sending e-mail from our system.

e-Dialog does not sell, share or rent the mailing list of our clients.

**Contacting Us**  
e-Dialog, Inc.  
65 Network Drive, Suite 400  
Burlington, MA 01803  
Phone: 888-256-7687  
E-mail: [privacypolicy@e-dialog.com](mailto:privacypolicy@e-dialog.com)

**Additional Resources**
